[Music]
being too crazy
thank you
these olives taste so good but they're
so salty now why is it because of my
Tears
olives have never tasted the same since
my lover since the Science Kid
[__] died
[Music]
oh well I don't give a [__] time to
watch Tamers one two three four five on
my laptop like I do everyday I shove all
shaped Foods down my throat
oh boy he released World War III how
come nobody told me I better run it back
so I can see how much asses I kicked
again my comorbius Lookout there's a
bullet coming right for you
wow
what I died before the fighting even
began this is [__] everyone knows I
defeated the new boys single-handedly
all by myself
I get it now the timeline diverged at
the exact moment I was shot am I am I
the key to all this
Gerald can you see me obviously dumbass
but why are you here I thought you were
dead
I was but I'm not anymore look what I'm
about to say may sound a little bit
complicated since we're only three years
old and still in kindergarten but in
short you and I are primordial beings
that were created by random people and
some [__] up room in my house
you're gonna have to repeat that I
didn't understand the damn thing
you and I are primordial beings that
were created by random people in some
[__] up room in my house
I [__] knew it that's why I think
Gerald why do you think others like
satch and kancho may get older while we
stay the same age why do you think the
Sonic Underground characters like Mindy
and dingo get birthday specials
we don't age life we've been three years
old for 648 years
648 years now I never thought about it
like that I just thought nobody ages
like us
that's cause you're [__] stupid
well we were there to see the birth of
Jesus Christ firsthand exactly now hurry
up and finish your olives and come over
to my house
hey there Rosy Cheeks don't mind me I
just got out of a steamy shower and got
done putting deodorant on my stinky bits
so talk to my pink ass what in the world
is going on
do you see the swab [__] this morning I
accidentally walked through it and ended
up in some [__] up room on the other
side what I saw that lies Beyond there
it can only be described as biblical
like the Sea of Eden and New Mexico
hey yo mommy where's my [__] pancakes
sit here awake I have something to show
you show me which I'm a scientist there
ain't nothing you can teach me up in
this [__] now give me pancakes there's
something weird going on with the wall I
was hoping you could explain what it is
the wall I'll get to the bottom of the
status I love you if I don't make it
back live call Gerald and tell him
someone must know my journey
no it cannot be it can't be true
I need to tell somebody about this or
else the whole world will be
[Music]
daddy daddy
what happened sexy baby there's some
kind of [__] up room in our house
[Music]
so tell me what did you see behind that
wall my smelly balls are itching to know
first answer me this Gerald do you have
any parents
what are you saying of course I do wait
no I I don't
then it's true life as we've known it as
a lie
but you have parents
because I'm the main character idiot you
don't have any because you're a side
character
also I never go to your house so they
were never programmed in
are you making fun of me I am not a side
character you piss color toddler
then why am I the Science Kid and you're
not
listen to my scientist Son fool
said smoking hot daddy but I thought you
were dead too
shut up
okay boys puddle together like football
players in case someone is listening in
it turns out we have all been living in
a virtual reality this whole time
I don't exactly know who or why someone
put us here
or why there's a [__] up room in my
house that I only somehow found
yesterday
but we all need to work together
just like the critically acclaimed Sonic
Underground wood
golly said I knew you were balls deep
with your hot dog in the moist cinnamon
buns of knowledge but I didn't know you
were this much of a science [__]
my baby boy as yellow as the sun don't
you think you're playing with fire
gross get off of me petto
my priority as a father is you see it
and if that means me living a lie so you
can be happy then so be it
curses it's seven already me and Gerald
have to get ready for school pups
but baby what about the plan
if we act different now the people
keeping us here will gross skeptical
love our plan
while I'm at school eating my celery
stick with peanut butter and raisins I
will try and think of a way to SK power
digital prison daddy you should hold
down the fort here for the time being
and Gerald I ripped a hole in my pants
so just say the word if you want a quick
[__]
have a fun day at school kids
you [__] [__] where's your mother
she was just getting you a bottle of
baby food where is she
oh
God
I always knew there was something foot
tip about you baby especially when you
watched Morpheus three times in a row
you killed my wife you took the love of
my life for me so now I'm going to take
your last breath
foreign
ER to fast for you baby
try again
you really suck
said was always the better child anyway
he has his own TV show what do you have
what do you have
I have the will to kill you father just
as I did Mommy
she was weak not even a challenge to
take out but you father are a worthy
challenge for my power
let's see how you fare against this you
sold less Ginger
go on then pull the trigger
I'm already laying drenched in my own
dirty waste of poop
besides I saw what was in the [__] up
room in our house
you can't kill me in a way that matters
I will haunt you forever
[Music]
hey Dad we're back from school
that why are you covered in [__]
it's a fetish thing so what did you
learn at school today
hey Sid smell my bop it stop it man
Gerald you are [__] up
okay so you notice how we only ever go
to three locations our house my school
and sometimes our backyard that's cause
those are the only three places which
exist in this virtual Realm
so that means a way to return to the
real world is in one of those three main
locations
hmm
I spent most of my time in my house and
my school's one room
so if there is an exit it is likely to
be in the backyard
wow that I never really noticed but you
got a pretty fat set of buns on your hub
they're like really big olives
I like your fat round olives
now are you boys ready to climb over the
fence and Escape
I sure am I've been waiting all day I
know me too
wait Sid what about our friends from
school
shut up Gerald you are balding at three
years old
better than Sonic the Hedgehog who has a
[__] mohawk and what of your mommy
and baby brother don't you love them
I love my mom my mom is cool but now
it's time to get the hell out of this
place
I can't tell Sia that I killed his baby
brother with a gun I think that might
ruin his day
Sid is right and the baby too he would
only slow us down more don't you agree
son
yeah perfect then get on your hands and
knees like you're getting real tiny from
behind I'm going to use your
three-year-old shoulders as a louder
well Sid's dad is it everything we
dreamed up
and what is it is it not a way out is it
still a vast virtual plane
we're not in a virtual simulation at all
we're just in [__] Ohio
then what about that [__] up room in
our house
how the [__] should I know it's every
man for himself now the [__] peace
out
wait Dad don't leave us
Sid the Science Kid we need to talk
[Music]
show me all the places I've never known
a world Chase
the night
race all of these broken dreams and
flights
foreign
[Music]